<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DevOps on Eddie Webbinaro</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/devops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DevOps on Eddie Webbinaro</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 12:41:05 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/devops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Organically DevOps: Building Quality and Security into the Software Supply Chain at Liberty Mutual</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/publications/alldaydevops/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/publications/alldaydevops/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This talk looked at Liberty Mutual’s transformation to Continuous Integration, Continuous Delivery, and DevOps. For a large, heavily regulated industry, this task can not only be daunting, but viewed by many as impossible. Often, organizations try to reduce the friction through micro-fixes, but Eddie’s team asked how to change the culture to reduce the friction and concluded with the following final points:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Don’t mandate DevOps. Give employees the chance to master their discipline with examples to set and follow.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Favor deep end-to-end accomplishments over broad but incremental steps forward. Focus on taking the right teams far before encouraging broad adoption.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Centralize the platforms and tools that your teams shouldn’t be thinking about. Provide foundational services/commodities and let teams stay on purpose.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Incorporate contributions from everyone; don’t stifle autonomy. Stay open to new ways of working.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Challenge security policies, but respect intentions. Find new ways to enforce concerns without abandoning precaution.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;allowfullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/FsfKsqI07jM?autoplay=0&amp;amp;controls=1&amp;amp;end=0&amp;amp;loop=0&amp;amp;mute=0&amp;amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSH release for Bamboo &amp; Remote Agents</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/creations/bosh-agents/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/creations/bosh-agents/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BOSH (Bosh Outer SHell) &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; is an open source tool for release engineering, deployment, lifecycle management, and monitoring of distributed systems.&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&amp;rdquo; And it&amp;rsquo;s amazingly powerful. This examples uses BOSH to provision an Alassian vendor app running on JDK along with the support Postgres database and agents to support it.  The releases manages the health of services and will automatically provision, start/stop processes across the various services.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian Marketplace Plugins</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/creations/marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/creations/marketplace/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Multiple plugins used by thousands of teams that provide enhanced functionality of Atlassian’s core products (primarily JIRA and Bamboo) to enrich CI/CD capabilities, DevOps automation, or productivity. Functionality spans user interface, web services and persistence.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
